var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "is given",
        "pcklId": "530",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "is given",
        "pcklId": "531",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a reward",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "ajrun",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "384",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "385",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَذِنَتْ",
        "answer": "And has listened",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wa-adhinat",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَذِنَتْ",
        "answer": "And has listened",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wa-adhinat",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "453",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "653",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "1407",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1408",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٍ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "alīmin",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2828",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "732",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "733",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "Then as for",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "But as for",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "548",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "549",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "ahlihi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "ahlihi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَشِّرْهُمْ",
        "answer": "so give them tidings",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "fabashir'hum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "baṣīran",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثُبُورًا",
        "answer": "(for) destruction",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "thubūran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَاسَبُ",
        "answer": "his account will be taken",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yuḥāsabu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابًا",
        "answer": "an account",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "ḥisāban",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحُقَّتْ",
        "answer": "and was obligated",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "waḥuqqat",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحُقَّتْ",
        "answer": "and was obligated",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "waḥuqqat",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحُورَ",
        "answer": "he would return",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaḥūra",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَخَلَّتْ",
        "answer": "and becomes empty",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "watakhallat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُو",
        "answer": "he will call",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "yadʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّهَا",
        "answer": "to its Lord",
        "pcklId": "939",
        "tlit": "lirabbihā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّهَا",
        "answer": "to its Lord",
        "pcklId": "940",
        "tlit": "lirabbihā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "941",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "942",
        "tlit": "rabbahu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَرْكَبُنَّ",
        "answer": "You will surely embark",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "latarkabunna",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْجُدُونَ",
        "answer": "they prostrate",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yasjudūna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْرُورًا",
        "answer": "happily",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "masrūran",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْرُورًا",
        "answer": "happy",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "masrūran",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَعِيرًا",
        "answer": "(in) a Blaze",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "saʿīran",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءُ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "tlit": "l-samāu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالشَّفَقِ",
        "answer": "by the twilight glow",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "bil-shafaqi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْشَقَّتْ",
        "answer": "is split asunder",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "inshaqqat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَصْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "And he will burn",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wayaṣlā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَبَقًا",
        "answer": "(to) stage",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ṭabaqan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَبَقٍ",
        "answer": "stage",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ṭabaqin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَّ",
        "answer": "(had) thought",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "ẓanna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَهْرِهِ",
        "answer": "his back",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ẓahrihi",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "of a punishment",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "biʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most knowing",
        "pcklId": "459",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُ",
        "answer": "never",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "ghayru",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرِئَ",
        "answer": "is recited",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "quri-a",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنُ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-qur'ānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُقْسِمُ",
        "answer": "I swear",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "uq'simu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَنْقَلِبُ",
        "answer": "And he will return",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wayanqalibu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَمَرِ",
        "answer": "And the moon",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "wal-qamari",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَهُ",
        "answer": "his record",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "kitābahu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَهُ",
        "answer": "his record",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "tlit": "kitābahu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَدْحًا",
        "answer": "(with) exertion",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kadḥan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَادِحٌ",
        "answer": "(are) laboring",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kādiḥun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَذِّبُونَ",
        "answer": "deny",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "yukadhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "had been",
        "pcklId": "1349",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "1350",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَلْقَتْ",
        "answer": "And has cast out",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "wa-alqat",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمُلَاقِيهِ",
        "answer": "and you (will) meet Him",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "famulāqīhi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "And the night",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "wa-al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُدَّتْ",
        "answer": "is spread",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "muddat",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَمْنُونٍ",
        "answer": "ending",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "mamnūnin",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَاءَ",
        "answer": "behind",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "warāa",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَقَ",
        "answer": "it envelops",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wasaqa",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّسَقَ",
        "answer": "it becomes full",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ittasaqa",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوعُونَ",
        "answer": "they keep within themselves",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yūʿūna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسِيرًا",
        "answer": "easy",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yasīran",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَمِينِهِ",
        "answer": "in his right (hand)",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "biyamīnihi",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "84",
        "ayah": "7"
    }
]; 
export default words;